Have you ever been in a lift with the big cheese in your company?
你有没有和公司的大人物一起坐过电梯？
It happened to me a couple of times.
这种事在我身上发生过几次。
And did I take advantage of the situation to deliver my elevator pitch?
我有没有利用这个机会做电梯自我推销？
Not a chance.
绝无可能。
He was surrounded by people buttering him up all the way to the top floor!
他被一群人围着奉承，一直到顶楼！
Lifts have an interesting history.
电梯有一段有趣的历史。
Today, the more important you are, the higher you live or work.
如今，你越重要，你居住或工作的地方就越高。
Penthouses have fantastic views for boardrooms and living rooms.
顶层公寓为会议室和客厅提供了绝佳的视野。
But it hasn't always been that way.
但过去并非总是如此。
Before the days of lifts, richer people would often prefer to live on the ground floor.
在电梯出现之前，富人通常更喜欢住在一楼。
Poorer people lived on the upper floors – and they had to use the stairs.
穷人则住在更高的楼层——因此他们不得不使用楼梯。
In any case, whatever your pay grade, the confined space of a lift makes for an awkward encounter.
无论如何，无论你的薪资级别如何，电梯狭小的空间必然导致尴尬的偶遇。
It's hard not to notice the uneasiness of a group of strangers in a confined space who have no time to develop any kind of bond.
很难注意不到一群陌生人在狭小空间中的不安，他们没有时间建立任何联系。
But if marketing people have their way, that's all going to change.
但如果营销人员得逞，这一切都将改变。
Jason Whale, sales manager at Elevators Ltd, says: "It's a very anxious experience the time you spend in a lift.
电梯有限公司的销售经理杰森·威尔（Jason Whale）说：“在电梯里度过时光是一种非常焦虑的体验。
If you have things around you, you take away that awkwardness.
如果你周围有东西，你会消除那种尴尬。
We all look at our phones sometimes or look down at the floor.
我们有时会看手机或低头看地板。
Well, surely it's better to look at advertisements on the walls…"
嗯，看墙上的广告肯定更好……”
He sees a lot of potential in this box in which we spend a few minutes every day.
他看到了这个我们每天花几分钟待着的“盒子”的巨大潜力。
Whale explains: "As technology becomes slimmer and cheaper, there are so many different ways to enhance a lift with light boxes, with moving images, with television screens!
威尔解释说：“随着技术变得更轻薄、更便宜，有很多不同的方式来增强电梯的功能，比如用灯箱、动态图像和电视屏幕！
It becomes quite exciting for us, and hopefully a little bit more interesting for the people who use lifts."
这对我们来说非常令人兴奋，也希望电梯使用者能觉得更有趣一些。”
Who knows what the lifts of the future will look like?
谁知道未来的电梯会是什么样子？
Perhaps they will become the places where everybody wants to be.
也许它们会成为每个人都想去的地方。
Time for a business meeting?
是时候开商务会议了吗？
Ready to party?
准备好派对了？
Come on everybody, let's get into the lift!
来吧，大家，我们进电梯吧！